for your future. How about for your
retirement?
Goal ready. Be goal ready for your dream
retirement. Enjoy life today while
building your retirement fund. Start
saving for as low as 66 pesos a day with
Manu Life Goal Ready.
>> Grammy, try my desserts. M pastries from
your new business.
Save up for your expansion.
Goal ready.
Be goal ready to scale up. Invest today
and grow your wealth with manual life's
diverse investment options. Please exit
goal ready. Be goal ready for your
child's education. Stay protected until
age 99 while securing your family's
future with Manu Life Goal Ready. Plan
the future you want today with Manu Life
Goal Ready. Visit manulife.com.ph PH to
learn more.
[Music]